Guide to the Archie Brown Papers ALBA.207
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: VALB: Bay Area Post
  - Nelson, Steve, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Nicaragua Ambulance Fund, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Nicaragua: Politics and Aid, 1984-1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Nicaragua: VALB trip to, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Nicaragua: Wheelchair Repair Workshop Project, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Oliver Law Scholarship Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association - Labor History Calendar (with Lincoln Brigade Photo), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Poetry: Proletariat and Spanish Civil War, undated, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Scottish Veterans, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Shirai, Jack, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Jonathan: Bequest, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Spain: Trip: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Spain: Homanaje a las Brigadas Internacionales, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Spain: Trip to Barcelona, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Spain: US Foreign Relations, undated, 1967-1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Spanish Civil War, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Spanish Civil War: American Participation: Student Paper with Annotations by Brown, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans: Clippings, 1977-1991 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans: Clippings (Spanish, Russian, Japanese), undated, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Spanish Strikers: VALB Support, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Tecnica: VALB Sponsorship, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Vietnam, undated, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Yates, James (Jimmy), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Series III: Oversize Material
  - House Committee on Un-American Activities: San Francisco Hearings and Protest: Clippings, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - World War II: Armed Forces Periodicals, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)